> > Brian Holt: 现在，我们有一个宠物组件，非常空。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So right now, we have this
pet component, it's pretty much empty.
我把里面的所有内容都删掉了
I deleted all the content inside of it so
you and
我要重写这一点让它看起来更棒
I are gonna rewrite this a little bit so
it looks a little bit nicer.
这就是宠物组件在搜索结果页面中显示的内容
So this is the pet component's gonna
show in the search results page,
将会在结果组件中使用。
which is gonna be used here
in the results component.
所以在名字动物品种
So at name, animal, breed, and
执行介质，位置和标识。
do media, location, and id.
我们会把它们从道具中拔出来
We'll pull those out of the props,
so they're gonna be passed down.
首先我们想做的是一个占位符图像
First thing we wanna have is a placeholder
image just in case, cuz some of these
动物实际上没有 >> Brian Holt: Images.
animals don't actually have
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Images.
所以我们要用我最喜欢的地方
So we're going to use place corgi
which is my favorite place to grab
占位符图像，我们将抓取 300 像素的像素图像，并且
placeholder images, and
we'll grab a 300 by 300 pixel image, and
那么我们就会说如果 ( 冥想长的话)
then we'll say if(media.length).
所以如果媒体是照片来的
So if media,
which is the photos coming in here,
对它有任何长度我们会说
has any length to it, and we'll say, yeah.
如果是平庸的话我们就会说英雄 = 媒体，
If media.length,
then we'll say hero = media,
0 是此处的第一个图像，是其中的小图像。
0 is the first image in here and
the small image inside of it.
这样我们就能找到第一幅图像
So that'll give us either the first
image that we can find or
看看这里的科尔吉
look at the place corgi.
然后我们要回来了一个 href
And then here,
we're going to return, a href, so
这将成为详细信息页面的链接
this is going to be a link
to the details page,
我想这将是我们共同编码的下一个问题
which will I think will be the next
thing that we'll code up together.
因此 /details/$  和
So /details/$  and
className="pet"。
className="pet".
在这种情况下，我们将使用类名为 "图像容器"的 div 。
Inside of that, we'll put a div
with className="image-container".
>> Brian Holt: 在此，源与英雄相等的图像
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And inside of that,
an image where the source is equal to hero
而高音等于宠物的名字。
and the alt is equal to
the name of the pet.
>> Brian Holt: 好，下面我们将有 div className="info"。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, beneath that
we'll have div className="info".
>> Brian Holt: 在其中，我们将有一个带有名称的 h1 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And inside of that,
we'll have an h1 with a name.
>> Brian Holt: 和 h2 ，此处我将使用模板字符串。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And h2, and
here I'm gonna use a template string.
您也可以在没有模板字符串的情况下执行此操作。
You also can do this
without template strings.
这对你很有影响我发现这跟模板弦比较容易
It's kinda up to you, I found this
easier to do with template strings.
所以我们要把动物 > Brian Holt:
So we're gonna put animal
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
然后破折号然后繁殖 > > Brian Holt: Then
then dash and then breed
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then
一个破折号和位置好吗
a dash and location, okay?
>> Brian Holt: 所以很多 React 程序都是这样的，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
a lot of React program looks like this,
它只是在构造标记，对吧 ?
where it's just constructing markup,
right?
一般的前端开发，一般都是这样的。
A lot of just front end development
in general kinda looks like this.
但现在如果我们回去看看我们的宠物组件
But now, if we go back over and
look at our pet component,
这应该看起来更宜人了
this should look a lot more pleasant.
我们去看看 " 收养我"
Let's go take a look at the Adopt Me.
我们会搜到一些东西你可以在这里看到
We'll search for something,
and you can see here,
我们要回各种宠物了
we're getting back all sorts of pets.
> > Brian Holt: 你可以在这里看到这些
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
you can see here that these corgi ones,
这些都是没有图象的
these are the ones that don't have images.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，请继续跳至此处的落实。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So go ahead and
jump up to the commit here.
如果你落后，这个承诺是， >> Brian Holt:
If you're behind, this commit was,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This one here,
异步调用 petfinder API，更新 Pet 组件。
async calls to Petfinder API,
update Pet component.
所以如果你能跳下去你就会被抓起来
So if you can jump forward to that commit,
you'll be caught up with me.